<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Fusion Networks</title>
    <link>http://localhost/fusionNetworks/www/index.php</link>
    <description>News from Fusion Networks</description>
    <item>
      <title>I wish that i had Jesses girrrrl</title>
      <link>http://localhost/fusionNetworks/www/index.php?page=newsItem&amp;id=69</link>
      <description>g35g35h4ht5 h</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeii</title>
      <link>http://localhost/fusionNetworks/www/index.php?page=newsItem&amp;id=63</link>
      <description>ba do doop bada, ba do doop bada</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pretty Girls</title>
      <link>http://localhost/fusionNetworks/www/index.php?page=newsItem&amp;id=31</link>
      <description>For now, it's a choice every buyer will have to make. You can have the far better-looking phone or you can have the slightly better-performing phone — and you really can't choose wrong. If the GS III is any indication, millions upon millions will choose the GS4. Me? I think design matters. Polish matters. The Galaxy S4 is fast and impressive, but it's also noisy and complex. The One is refined, quiet, comfortable, beautiful, and above all simply pleasant. I love using that phone, in a way I haven't experienced with anything since the iPhone 5. That's why, when my contract is up in June, I'll probably be casting my lot with HTC instead of Samsung.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greenheart</title>
      <link>http://localhost/fusionNetworks/www/index.php?page=newsItem&amp;id=39</link>
      <description>As major game publishers push overbearing copy protection that frustrates legitimate players, an indie studio has taken a novel approach to the difficult problem of piracy. Greenheart Games released a "cracked" version of its Game Dev Tycoon to illegal downloading sites, but there's a sting in the tail — anyone attempting to play the game development simulation beyond a few hours will get a subtle hint about the consequences of their actions. A message informs the player that people are choosing to pirate their studio's game, and profits will drop until the virtual company eventually goes bankrupt.&#13;
&#13;
In a blog post, Patrick Klug of Greenheart Games said that the cracked version made up over 93 percent of all Game Dev Tycoon downloads, and highlighted the frustrated response of players who were experiencing the struggles of piracy first-hand.&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Greenheart Games isn't the first developer to adopt unorthodox anti-piracy measures. Crysis Warhead replaced bullets with considerably less effective chickens upon detecting a crack, for example, and illicit copies of Michael Jackson: The Experience on Nintendo DS drowned out the music with incessant vuvuzela blasts. Nintendo took a subtler approach with its SNES RPG EarthBound; pirated versions of the game ramped up the number of enemies, and if a player somehow managed to make it to the final boss, their save file would be deleted. Still, the meta nature of Greenheart Games' solution has to be appreciated — the studio is taking a unique opportunity to confront pirates about the effect they can have on game development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeii</title>
      <link>http://localhost/fusionNetworks/www/index.php?page=newsItem&amp;id=40</link>
      <description>As major game publishers push overbearing copy protection that frustrates legitimate players, an indie studio has taken a novel approach to the difficult problem of piracy. Greenheart Games released a "cracked" version of its Game Dev Tycoon to illegal downloading sites, but there's a sting in the tail — anyone attempting to play the game development simulation beyond a few hours will get a subtle hint about the consequences of their actions. A message informs the player that people are choosing to pirate their studio's game, and profits will drop until the virtual company eventually goes bankrupt.&#13;
&#13;
In a blog post, Patrick Klug of Greenheart Games said that the cracked version made up over 93 percent of all Game Dev Tycoon downloads, and highlighted the frustrated response of players who were experiencing the struggles of piracy first-hand.&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Greenheart Games isn't the first developer to adopt unorthodox anti-piracy measures. Crysis Warhead replaced bullets with considerably less effective chickens upon detecting a crack, for example, and illicit copies of Michael Jackson: The Experience on Nintendo DS drowned out the music with incessant vuvuzela blasts. Nintendo took a subtler approach with its SNES RPG EarthBound; pirated versions of the game ramped up the number of enemies, and if a player somehow managed to make it to the final boss, their save file would be deleted. Still, the meta nature of Greenheart Games' solution has to be appreciated — the studio is taking a unique opportunity to confront pirates about the effect they can have on game development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Good Q1 Profits</title>
      <link>http://localhost/fusionNetworks/www/index.php?page=newsItem&amp;id=42</link>
      <description>As major game publishers push overbearing copy protection that frustrates legitimate players, an indie studio has taken a novel approach to the difficult problem of piracy. Greenheart Games released a "cracked" version of its Game Dev Tycoon to illegal downloading sites, but there's a sting in the tail — anyone attempting to play the game development simulation beyond a few hours will get a subtle hint about the consequences of their actions. A message informs the player that people are choosing to pirate their studio's game, and profits will drop until the virtual company eventually goes bankrupt.&#13;
&#13;
In a blog post, Patrick Klug of Greenheart Games said that the cracked version made up over 93 percent of all Game Dev Tycoon downloads, and highlighted the frustrated response of players who were experiencing the struggles of piracy first-hand.&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Greenheart Games isn't the first developer to adopt unorthodox anti-piracy measures. Crysis Warhead replaced bullets with considerably less effective chickens upon detecting a crack, for example, and illicit copies of Michael Jackson: The Experience on Nintendo DS drowned out the music with incessant vuvuzela blasts. Nintendo took a subtler approach with its SNES RPG EarthBound; pirated versions of the game ramped up the number of enemies, and if a player somehow managed to make it to the final boss, their save file would be deleted. Still, the meta nature of Greenheart Games' solution has to be appreciated — the studio is taking a unique opportunity to confront pirates about the effect they can have on game development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truck Driver</title>
      <link>http://localhost/fusionNetworks/www/index.php?page=newsItem&amp;id=46</link>
      <description>A Mid North stock-truck driver had to leap to safety when his cab burst into flames on State Highway 12 in the Far North.&#13;
&#13;
The blaze yesterday left the 33-year-old from Kaikohe with minor burns to one hand and destroyed the cab.&#13;
&#13;
It also closed the highway 2km west of the Taheke bridge, first as firefighters doused the flames and again as the wreck was removed.&#13;
&#13;
No animals were on board at the time.&#13;
&#13;
Senior Constable Jeff Cramp, of Rawene police, said the driver was heading to Kouto Pt, South Hokianga, to pick up cattle and take them to Te Kuiti.&#13;
&#13;
Driving west out of Kaikohe, he twice pulled over to investigate an electrical burning smell but could find nothing.&#13;
&#13;
About 10.30am, however, just past Taheke, smoke poured from the dashboard. By the time he stopped the truck and threw out his bag, the cab was burning fiercely and he had to jump to safety.&#13;
&#13;
With no time to find a safe place to pull over, the blazing truck was left blocking the highway's westbound lane. The driver suffered a minor burn to one hand but did not require medical treatment.&#13;
&#13;
With no cellphone coverage in the area and no landline at the nearest house, the driver then had to run along the road until he had enough reception to make a 111 call.&#13;
&#13;
The highway was closed for 45 minutes while one appliance from Rawene Fire Brigade and two from Kaikohe doused the burning cab.&#13;
&#13;
Mr Cramp said the driver was ``quite distraught''. He had looked after the truck as if it was his own.&#13;
&#13;
A specialist tow truck from Whangarei was due to remove the burnt-out wreck yesterday afternoon.&#13;
&#13;
Mr Cramp said it was fortunate no cattle were on board at the time.&#13;
&#13;
``If there is, the only option you've got is to open up the back and let the stock out on to the road.''&#13;
&#13;
The Rawene police officer said he had been to one such accident where spooked cattle had to be let out on to a highway. The result was carnage, he said.&#13;
&#13;
Initial indications were that the cause of the fire was electrical.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
